<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Research Bazaar Victoria</title>
    <description>Run by a team from Monash eResearch Centre, Research Bazaar (ResBaz for short) is a skill- and community-building festival where HDR students and early career researchers come together to learn the latest in digital research tools and digital scholarship.</description>
    <link>http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>ResBazVic 2024 Welcomes New Sponsors</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ResBaz Victoria is thrilled to announce and welcome its newly confirmed sponsors, the Australian Research Data Commons (ARDC), GALE, and AARNet. Thank you for your support and interest in engaging with Monash and the Australian ResBaz community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Organising Committee will soon be calling for Expressions of Interest for those who want to get involved, whether by running a workshop, giving a talk, or volunteering to chair a session. If you already have ideas on how to participate, please reach out to us at ResBazVIC-l@monash.edu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently finalising details, so please watch out for upcoming updates.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/welcomes-new-sponsors</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/welcomes-new-sponsors</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ResBazVic 2024 Dates and Venue Confirmed</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve now confirmed dates and venue for ResBazVic 2024 - Monash University Clayton campus on 26th to 28th November. The organising team is working hard putting together a packed program for you, so check back here for updates.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/resbaz-save-the-date</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/resbaz-save-the-date</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
