<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Research Bazaar Victoria</title>
    <description>Run by a team of volunteers from south-east Queensland universities, Research Bazaar (ResBaz for short) is a skill- and community-building festival where HDR students and early career researchers come together to learn the latest in digital research tools and digital scholarship.</description>
    <link>http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>ResBaz Newsletter #4</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi ResBazzers, the countdown to ResBazQld 2023 is well and truly underway now, and we’re getting ready to welcome you to UQ’s St Lucia campus on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, our regular reminder to please &lt;a href=&quot;https://resbaz.github.io/resbaz2023qld/blog/workshop-booking-open&quot;&gt;book your workshop places&lt;/a&gt; (and thank you to those of you who have already done so). Many of the workshops &lt;strong&gt;will&lt;/strong&gt; book out, and entry to those will be limited to those who have signed up in advance. So if you don’t want to miss out, get your bookings in now!!!! &lt;a href=&quot;https://resbaz.github.io/resbaz2023qld/schedule/&quot;&gt;Check out the schedule&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://resbaz.github.io/resbaz2023qld/blog/workshop-booking-open&quot;&gt;follow these instructions&lt;/a&gt; to guarantee your spot. And remember that a few workshops run over multiple sessions, so don’t double-book yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As well as the scheduled program of workshops and talks, there are plenty of other activities going on over ResBazQld. Two highlights of these will be our social evening on Wednesday and “Hacky Corner” every breaktime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The social evening will be held at Belltop Café 5.30 – 7.30pm on Wednesday, and we hope many of you will join us there for nibbles and drinks, and of course watching or taking part in the legendary “90 Seconds of Research Impact” challenge. Did we mention there will be &lt;strong&gt;prizes&lt;/strong&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hacky Corner is an extension of the popular “Hacky Hour” that takes place at nearly all Queensland universities. It’s a casual drop-in help community running each break time, where our volunteer team will try to answer any and all of your research computing related questions. Look out for the signs in the exhibitors/catering area and ask away! And if you’re a programmer/HPC user/data manager or any other support specialist or experienced user who likes helping others, come along too and share your expertise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget, &lt;a href=&quot;https://events.humanitix.com/resbazqld-2023&quot;&gt;registration will stay open&lt;/a&gt; for the rest of the week, so if your friends haven’t registered yet, let them know they can still join in the fun!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See you soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kind regards, from the ResBazQld team (resbaz@qcif.edu.au)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow @ResBazQld on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/resbazqld&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/resbazqld/&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/newsletter-4</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/newsletter-4</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ResBaz Newsletter #3</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello ResBazzers, just one week to go now to ResBazQld 2023!!! With it getting very near now, we’ll be sending you several information emails over the next few days - 
sorry about any repeated information, but we want to make sure that you have all the details needed to make the most of this event. And for even more hints and tips 
about how to get the most out of ResBazQld, make sure to follow us at @ResBazQld on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/resbazqld&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/resbazqld/&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, where our mascot “Bazza the ResBaz bear” will be giving you daily updates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most importantly at this stage, make sure you’ve signed up for any workshops that you want to attend - many are getting very full already. Take a look at 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://resbaz.github.io/resbaz2023qld/schedule/&quot;&gt;the program&lt;/a&gt;, decide what sessions you like, and 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://resbaz.github.io/resbaz2023qld/blog/workshop-booking-open&quot;&gt;book yourself a place&lt;/a&gt;. Remember, don’t double book yourself if you sign-up for one of 
the multi-session workshops (Programming with Python, R for scientific analysis, or Introduction to image analysis with FIJI)!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost as importantly, there are plenty of PRIZES to be won at ResBaz, so make sure you get involved to give yourself the best chance to win! Some of our competitions 
include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A lucky door prize for each of our key story speaker sessions. Not to mention that they’ll all be amazing talks anyway!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The “Ninety Seconds of Research Impact” competition during our social reception on Wednesday evening. All you have to do is tell us about your research in 90 seconds or less - no props, no slides, just you and a microphone!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Our networking games and competitions - ResBaz Bingo, the Name Badge Challenge, the Acronym Game, and the Data Science Riddle. More on those next week!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, one of our key story speakers – Professor Michael Milford from QUT – has given us a sneak preview of his talk in 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/michaeljmilford_artificialintelligence-careeradvice-careers-activity-7127852675492171776-67_4&quot;&gt;this post&lt;/a&gt;; check it out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See you all next week, and remember there is still &lt;a href=&quot;https://events.humanitix.com/resbazqld-2023&quot;&gt;time to register&lt;/a&gt;, so let your friends know if they haven’t already signed up!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kind regards, from the ResBaz Qld team (resbaz@qcif.edu.au)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/newsletter-3</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/newsletter-3</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ResBaz Newsletter #2</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello ResBazzers, ResBazQld 2023 is getting near now and we’re starting to get excited about it – we hope you are too! So that you can get the most out of your three days, 
here’s a few suggestions from us to help you prepare. And while you’re doing that, make sure you encourage your friends and colleagues to register as well – there are 
still tickets available and at ResBaz it’s “the more the merrier”, so please spread the word.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday evening, we’ll be holding a social event at UQ’s Belltop Café, featuring the return of ResBaz favourite: “Ninety Seconds of Research Impact”. All you have 
to do is tell us about your research in 90 seconds or less - no props, no slides, just you and a microphone! So start planning and practicing your talk now - there are 
prizes! Talking of prizes, we’ve got daily competitions and lucky door tickets, so you have even more chances to win stuff!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very important - if you haven’t done so already, don’t forget to plan your schedule and sign up for any workshops you want to attend before they book out; your registration 
includes the workshops, but you &lt;em&gt;must&lt;/em&gt; book a place to be able to attend. Take a &lt;a href=&quot;https://resbaz.github.io/resbaz2023qld/schedule/&quot;&gt;look at the program&lt;/a&gt;, decide what sessions 
you like, and register using the links on our &lt;a href=&quot;https://resbaz.github.io/resbaz2023qld/blog/workshop-booking-open&quot;&gt;booking page&lt;/a&gt;. Remember, don’t double book yourself if you 
sign-up for one of the multi-session workshops (Programming with Python, R for scientific analysis, or Introduction to image analysis with FIJI)!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, ResBaz wouldn’t be possible without the generous support of our sponsors – &lt;a href=&quot;https://ardc.edu.au/&quot;&gt;ARDC&lt;/a&gt;, 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gale.com/intl/primary-sources/digital-scholar-lab&quot;&gt;Gale&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://learningresources.sagepub.com/home&quot;&gt;Sage&lt;/a&gt;. Please take a moment to visit their websites, 
and have a chat with them at their exhibitor booths during the week, to thank them for being an important part of ResBaz.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you all soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/newsletter-2</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/newsletter-2</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Book your workshop places</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;resbaz-workshop-bookings-are-open&quot;&gt;ResBaz workshop bookings are open&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have registered for ResBaz, you need to book into the workshops of your choice. 
All workshop bookings are &lt;strong&gt;free of charge&lt;/strong&gt;, but most have limited capacity so we can 
only let you into that workshop if you have booked a place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Decide on your &lt;a href=&quot;https://resbaz.github.io/resbaz2023qld/schedule/&quot;&gt;schedule&lt;/a&gt;, then click
the links below to go to the relevant booking pages. You will need to have your &lt;strong&gt;ResBaz
order number&lt;/strong&gt; handy when booking - this is just below the QR code in your ResBaz
registration confirmation email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VERY IMPORTANT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Three of the workshops (Programming with Python, R for Scientific Analysis, 
and Introduction to Image Analysis with FIJI) run over multiple sessions, and you are 
expected to attend all sessions if you register for these subjects. You only need to 
register for the first session, but that booking will apply to all sessions. &lt;strong&gt;DO NOT&lt;/strong&gt; 
book for other workshops at the same times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Session &lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Workshop&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Time&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Link&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session 1&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;- Programming with Python&lt;br /&gt;- R for scientific analysis&lt;br /&gt;- Helping HASS students answer the question: Do you need the digital in your research?&lt;br /&gt;- Evaluating AI apps for your literature reviews&lt;br /&gt;- Dealing with impostor syndrome: You are not alone&lt;br /&gt;- Your research toolkit in the cloud&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tue 21 Nov&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;9:00 am&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://events.humanitix.com/session-1-tuesday-9-00-10-30&quot;&gt;Book a place&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session 2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;- Demystifying AI for research&lt;br /&gt;- Exploring genomic data with the Australian Reference Genome Atlas&lt;br /&gt;- Guided networking session&lt;br /&gt;- Tips for moving from desktop to HPC&lt;br /&gt;- Programming with Python (cont.)&lt;br /&gt;- R for scientific analysis (cont.)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;  Tue 21 Nov&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;11:00 am&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://events.humanitix.com/session-2-tuesday-11-00-12-30&quot;&gt;Book a place&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session 3&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;- Introducing computational thinking&lt;br /&gt;- Research Infrastructure: The Secret Third Thing&lt;br /&gt;- AI summarisation and retrieval pipelines for research&lt;br /&gt;- FAIR and CARE data: principles for responsible and ethical research&lt;br /&gt;- Transferable skills: Understanding failure, strengths and values&lt;br /&gt;- Reproducible research in R&lt;br /&gt;- R for scientific analysis (cont.)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Tue 21 Nov&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;3:00 pm&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://events.humanitix.com/session-3-tuesday-15-00-17-00&quot;&gt;Book a place&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session 4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;- TERN services to share, discover and access ecosystem data&lt;br /&gt;- Data organisation in spreadsheets for researchers&lt;br /&gt;- Statistics proficiency: Brainstorm about needs, resources and gaps&lt;br /&gt;- Introduction to image analysis with FIJI&lt;br /&gt;- Programming with Python (cont.)&lt;br /&gt;- R for scientific analysis (cont.)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wed 22 Nov&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;9:00 am&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://events.humanitix.com/session-4-wednesday-9-00-10-30&quot;&gt;Book a place&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session 5&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;- Generating graphs using Python and ChatGPT&lt;br /&gt;- Network know-how &amp;amp; data handling&lt;br /&gt;- Introduction to data cleaning with OpenRefine&lt;br /&gt;- Show ‘em what you’ve got: building an authentic profile for academic and industry impact&lt;br /&gt;- Introduction to image analysis with FIJI (cont.)&lt;br /&gt;- R for scientific analysis (cont.)&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wed 22 Nov&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;11:00 am&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://events.humanitix.com/session-5-wednesday-11-00-12-30&quot;&gt;Book a place&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session 6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;- Introduction to Jupyter Notebooks&lt;br /&gt;- Introduction to chrono-urbanism and spatial networks in R&lt;br /&gt;- Unlock the power of text analytics with LADAL&lt;br /&gt;- Quantum machine learning&lt;br /&gt;- Nanopore sequencing in human genomics&lt;br /&gt;- UQRUG presents: Cool but useless&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Wed 22 Nov&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;3:00 pm&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://events.humanitix.com/session-6-wednesday-15-00-17-00&quot;&gt;Book a place&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session 7&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;- Shell basics for HPC&lt;br /&gt;- R Shiny Essentials: From Data to Interactive Dashboards&lt;br /&gt;- Storing and querying your research data with a database&lt;br /&gt;- Advanced data wrangling with OpenRefine&lt;br /&gt;- Copyright considerations for human researchers&lt;br /&gt;- How Bazaar, How Bazaar: Let’s think about ChatGPT, et.al&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thurs 23 Nov&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;9:00 am&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://events.humanitix.com/session-7-thursday-9-00-10-30&quot;&gt;Book a place&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session 8&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;- Boosting your wellbeing&lt;br /&gt;- Uplift your instructing skills: Hints and tips from The Carpentries instructor program&lt;br /&gt;- Using the Gale Digital Scholar Lab to explore primary sources in the Age of Enlightenment&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thurs 23 Nov&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;11:00 am&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://events.humanitix.com/session-8-thursday-11-00-12-30&quot;&gt;Book a place&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session 9&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;- Phylogenomics analysis based on Linux command line environment&lt;br /&gt;- Introduction to spatial analysis in R&lt;br /&gt;- Web archiving for data collection&lt;br /&gt;- Collecting and analysing YouTube and Newstalk data&lt;br /&gt;- Looking for ongoing 1-on-1 mentorship after ResBaz? Start here!&lt;br /&gt;- RIMReP data management system: All GBR data in one single place&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Thurs 23 Nov&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;3:00 pm&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://events.humanitix.com/session-9-thursday-15-00-17-00&quot;&gt;Book a place&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/workshop-booking-open</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/workshop-booking-open</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ResBaz Newsletter #1</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;ResBazQld 2023 is now only a couple of weeks away now, so it’s time to start planning your ResBaz activities!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have heaps going on every day, but most of our workshops do have limited capacity so you will need to book to ensure your place. Have a look at our 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://resbaz.github.io/resbaz2023qld/schedule/&quot;&gt;schedule&lt;/a&gt;, decide what sessions you want to attend, and go to 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://resbaz.github.io/resbaz2023qld/blog/workshop-booking-open&quot;&gt;the booking information page&lt;/a&gt; to find registration links.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the workshops run over multiple sessions, so please make sure you don’t double-book yourself! And we expect many of them to be very popular, so 
get in early before spaces fill up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are still tickets available for ResBaz, and because we’re all about community and connections, the more people who can join us the better. So please 
tell all your friends and colleagues, and encourage them to come along too. They’re not going to find better value than a three day conference for $40 with 
food, drink, evening social event, and prizes included!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you all soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/newsletter-1</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/newsletter-1</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ResBazQld 2023 dates and venue confirmed</title>
        <description>&lt;h4 id=&quot;resbazqld-2023-save-the-date&quot;&gt;ResBazQld 2023 Save the Date&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-
We’ve now confirmed dates and venue for ResBazQld 2023 - The University of Queensland St Lucia campus on 21st to 23rd November. The organising team are hard at work putting together a packed program for you, so check back here for updates.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/resbaz-save-the-date</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/resbaz-save-the-date</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ResBazQld Key Story talks now available to view</title>
        <description>&lt;h4 id=&quot;resbazqld-key-story-talks-now-available-to-view&quot;&gt;ResBazQld Key Story talks now available to view&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All ResBazQld Key Story talks are now available to view or download. All except Tim Sherratt’s talk will require a password to view or download. The password will be emailed to all registered ResBazQld attendees today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;opening-address--dr-julia-playford-executive-director-of-science-development-queensland-department-of-environment-and-science&quot;&gt;Opening Address – Dr Julia Playford, Executive Director of Science Development, Queensland Department of Environment and Science.&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Video link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/652703318&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/652703318&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;br /&gt;
Download link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/user82369617/download/652703318/7ae5f90aa2&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/user82369617/download/652703318/7ae5f90aa2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;exploring-australian-galleries-libraries-archives-and-museums--associate-professor-tim-sherratt-university-of-canberra&quot;&gt;Exploring Australian Galleries Libraries Archives and Museums – Associate Professor Tim Sherratt, University of Canberra&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slides for the talk are available at &lt;a href=&quot;https://slides.com/wragge/resbaz-2021&quot;&gt;https://slides.com/wragge/resbaz-2021&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Video link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/652696272&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/652696272&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Download link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/user82369617/download/652696272/a616cb2c5c&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/user82369617/download/652696272/a616cb2c5c&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;soils-4-science--dr-zeinab-khalil-senior-research-fellow-at-the-institute-for-molecular-bioscience-at-the-university-of-queensland-and-program-manager-for-soils-4-science&quot;&gt;Soils 4 Science – Dr Zeinab Khalil, Senior Research Fellow at the Institute for Molecular Bioscience at The University of Queensland, and Program manager for Soils 4 Science.&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apologies for the lack of sound for the first two -three minutes. The sound for the video at the end didn’t capture well on the microphone – the original of that video can be viewed at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d20hQA18tLw&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d20hQA18tLw&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soils 4 Science project: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imb.uq.edu.au/soilsforscience&quot;&gt;https://imb.uq.edu.au/soilsforscience&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;
Video link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/652706726&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/652706726&lt;/a&gt;     &lt;br /&gt;
Download link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/user82369617/download/652706726/3fa43e06a0&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/user82369617/download/652706726/3fa43e06a0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;the-life-of-survey-data-from-conception-to-birth-then-graduation-culminating-in-its-life-purpose--doing-surveys-well-by-design--associate-professor-sama-low-choy--senior-statistician-at-griffith-university&quot;&gt;The Life of Survey Data: From Conception to Birth then Graduation, Culminating in its Life Purpose / Doing Surveys Well, By Design – Associate Professor Sama Low-Choy,  Senior Statistician at Griffith University&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Video link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/652709985&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/652709985&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;
Download link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/user82369617/download/652709985/d1912185ba&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/user82369617/download/652709985/d1912185ba&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;nature-conservation---professor-hugh-possingham-queensland-chief-scientist&quot;&gt;Nature Conservation - Professor Hugh Possingham, Queensland Chief Scientist.&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Video link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/652699884&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/652699884&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;
Download link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/user82369617/download/652699884/798aea410f&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/user82369617/download/652699884/798aea410f&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;the-importance-of-engagement--dr-peter-binks-vice-president-industry-and-external-engagement-griffith-university&quot;&gt;The Importance of Engagement – Dr Peter Binks, Vice-President, Industry and External Engagement, Griffith University.&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Video link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/652704846&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/652704846&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;
Download link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/user82369617/download/652704846/3f5530c574&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/user82369617/download/652704846/3f5530c574&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;the-gale-digital-scholar-lab---getting-started-with-your-research---damian-almeida-training-executive-gale-cengage&quot;&gt;The Gale Digital Scholar Lab - Getting started with your research - Damian Almeida, Training Executive, Gale Cengage.&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Video link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/652721652&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/652721652&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;
Download link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/user82369617/download/652721652/e94c96abe0&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/user82369617/download/652721652/e94c96abe0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/resbaz-talks-now-live</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://118.138.242.96:4000/resbazvic2024/blog/resbaz-talks-now-live</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
